Papa! This one!
Let's see. Ah, Yun Yun the
Servant and Pudding the Witch.
You really do love this book, don't you?
Yup!
I dunno why, but when
you read me this book,
I can sleep real good!
Well, that's good.
All right, Papa will read it for
you, so make sure you sleep soundly.
Yay!
Your Majesty!
Why are you shirking your
duties and putting Lady Doux to bed?
It's still noon! Noon!
Don't be such a spoilsport.
There's no harm in coming to see
Doux during her nap time, is there?
There is! You still have
a mountain of work to do!
I'm sorry, Doux.
That sound...
Doux!
What?!
Oh, I've missed you so, Doux!
Just look how big you've gotten!
Wh-Wh-Wh-What is the meaning of this?!
I-I'm Jahi!
Huh?
Ah! So you've returned from
your world conquest, Dahaka!
Darling!
Th-This is the great Azi Dahaka?
The dragon of calamity who can bring about
catastrophes powerful enough to
destroy gods that is
conquering the world by herself.
And she's Lady Doux's...
mother?!
THE DEMON KING'S WIFE LOVES
HER DAUGHTER TOO MUCH!!
"The Demon King's Wife Loves
Her Daughter Too Much!!"
Dahaka...
How goes world domination?
Well, it didn't work out.
Even though we were apart, my heart
as a mother grew even fonder...
And I even ended up feeling
love for a human child.
I had no time for conquering anything!
Yes! I know exactly how that feels!
Okay, so they're both doting parents.
Lady Doux?
Doux! There you are!
I'm home! Come here! It's your mama!
Hello...
D-D-D-Doux?
Wh-Wh-Why are you acting
like we've never met before?
Ah, I feared this would happen.
What do you mean, Your Majesty?
Doux doesn't remember Dahaka.
It was inevitable.
Dahaka left to conquer the world before
Doux was old enough to remember.
Wh-What is that?!
Th-This is bad! That's
Dahaka's power at work.
Depending on Dahaka's mood, she can bring
about all kinds of great disasters!
What?!
Why is there suddenly a storm?!
Run away!
I-It's all right, Lady Dahaka!
I'm sure Lady Doux will
remember you very soon.
Jahi is right.
Oh, I know!
Why don't you play with
Doux like you used to?
That might help her remember.
Th-That's a brilliant idea!
Now, let's go, Lady Dahaka!
You're right!
She's sure to remember
me if we play together.
That was close...
But it appears that Doux is unsure
how to interact with her mother.
I hope she is able to remember
something as they're playing.
This takes me back.
We used to walk on the beach like this.
Do you remember, Doux?
Nuh-uh.
I-I see...
Oh, dear...
Dahaka! Perhaps she'll remember
if you two have a little race.
O-Of course.
I guess Doux is able
to walk by herself now.
All right! Let's race to those rocks!
I had forgotten.
She...
has absolutely no idea how to hold back.
I made a lot, so eat up!
You used to love these sweets,
so I made them for you all the time.
Do you remember?
But...
they're really yummy.
I see...
She said that she would like
to be alone for a while.
I see.
I'm sure that it was quite a shock
that Doux didn't remember anything.
Or rather, perhaps it's
regret rather than shock.
Huh? What do you mean?
Before, Dahaka was a single
dragon bent on world domination.
But she had an evil side that
wanted to take over the world
and a gentle side that brought
blessings and healing to the world.
And since I needed the
powers of her evil side,
I used a bracelet called the
Heavenly Ring of Evil...
and split her into two beings,
one evil and one good.
And they are... Doux and Dahaka.
What?!
Y-Y-Y-You never told me that before!
I'm sure you're surprised.
But that means neither of
us are technically her parents.
However...
I thank you, Ahriman.
Now I can concentrate on taking over
the world without any distractions.
That's right...
I have no need for a good heart!
Mama!
Papa!
Huh?
It was Doux's first words
that made us family.
I-I had no idea that Lady
Doux had such a secret.
And so, I decided to raise
Doux into a proper demon.
But Dahaka believed that
her love for Doux would get in the way
of her ambition for world domination,
so she left on a journey
alone to take over the world.
I'm certain that she
regrets that decision.
By the way, where is Lady Doux?
Doux...
Are you okay?
I'm fine. I was just having
some trouble sleeping.
Then Doux will read this for you!
What?
I brought a picture book!
If I read this, you'll calm down.
Let's see...
"Once upon a time, there
was a servamp named Yun Yun
and a m-musician? Named Pudding.
Pudding always"... Um...
Let me see it. I'll read it with you.
Really?!
Let's see...
"Once upon a time, there
was a servant named Yun Yun
and a magician named Pudding.
Pudding always did bad things,
and Yun Yun was always crying.
Despite how they were, they didn't
actually dislike each other.
Then one day..."
This book...
So when Papa reads me this picture book,
even after I fall asleep, someone
reads it in my dreams, too.
I couldn't remember who that was...
but now I remember!
Yes... Right.
Okay, how about I read the
rest of the book for you then?
"LET'S READ THE PICTURE BOOK"
LYRICS: KANATA NAKAMURA
COMPOSITION AND ARRANGEMENT: NAOKI YANAGISAWA
SONG: DOUX
Yay!
Okay, go change into your pajamas.
Okay!
There's someone just
beyond my fluffy dreams
I wonder who it is
They have a really, really kind voice
As they speak to me
Only my fuzzy memories came to me before
But now, I think I remember
Mama, Mama
That word fills me with joy
I want to call to her even more
"And so, Pudding the Witch
disappeared into the night sky.
The end."
Hmm?
Welcome back, Mama!
I'm home now, Doux.
THE FACE REVEAL CEREMONY IS TOO SOON!!
"The Face Reveal Ceremony Is Too Soon!!"
The Face Reveal Ceremony.
A ceremony carried out by
demons since time immemorial.
It is a tradition where the demon
king's heir reveals their face
to all in the demon castle
when they are still young.
Doux was about to undergo this ceremony.
I'm going now!
Make sure you come back for lunch!
Okay!
Lady Dahaka!
H-Have you seen Lady Doux?
I've been looking everywhere for her!
Doux just left for a walk just now.
A walk? But she has no time for that!
The Face Reveal Ceremony is soon!
I need Lady Doux to properly act
like the demon king's daughter
and to memorize her lines immediately!
Dahaka!
I'm so worried!
Will Doux actually be able to
stand in front of a huge crowd
and properly say her lines?
Perhaps we should just do this
in front of the ones we know.
Your Majesty!
More importantly, Lady Doux
needs to do her dress rehearsal!
What do you mean, "More importantly"?!
What if this traumatizes her?!
There you go babying her again!
Your Majesty, this is all because...
Sometimes, you're far
too strict with Doux!
Calm down, both of you.
Yes, ma'am.
Honestly...
If you two, who are the closest to her,
don't believe in her, then who will?
But...
If you're that worried, then
go find Doux right now.
You'll know immediately that
there's no need to worry.
Find Lady Doux?
Granny! I got lots of big cormbs!
My, those are fine corn cobs.
Then why don't we let you take those?
Really?!
Well, you're always helping me out.
Let me at least do this for you.
Thanks!
Lady Doux...
We came here as Lady Dahaka insisted,
and Lady Doux is already helping a human!
I had no idea Doux came to
a village so far away again.
Why are you impressed?
I cannot agree with Lady Dahaka.
There are far too many things
to do before the ceremony.
There's no time for this! Wha—
Wait, wait, Jahi!
Let's watch for a little while
longer before we decide.
Which one has the present?
Um...
The right one!
Come on, Mayu! Doux gets to go first.
Shut up! I'm gonna beat Doux this time!
Jeez...
Doux picks this one.
Hm...
Then Doux is our winner!
What?!
Wow! Chocolate!
Hey! You cheated just now, didn't you?
Santa only rewards the good kids.
Damn it! You'll pay for this!
Here.
Wh-Wha...
You don't seem too disappointed.
You must be in the spring of your youth.
What?!
Of course. He skipped out on his
angel duties to come see Doux.
Sh-Shut up! You two are in the same boat!
We're on break.
It's not Santa season right now.
Don't lump us in with you.
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
That halo... He couldn't be.
Stupid! Stupid!
Also, did she just say "Santa"?
Wh-Who does that greenhorn think he is?!
How dare he share some
chocolate with Doux?!
Please calm down, Your Majesty.
Hey! There's barely any
ingredients in here!
There's not enough milk or seafood at all!
When are we supposed to get more?
W-Well, Chef...
We're having some trouble
with our vendor...
What?! You can't be serious!
I'm putting my life on the line cooking!
Ugh, what am I supposed to do?
This isn't going to do at all...
Master.
Huh?
Here you go.
Doux? This is for me?
Yup! I heard you this morning
saying there wasn't any food.
The cormbs from Granny's fields
are super sweet and yummy.
They'll go with anything!
Doux...
Doux!
B-But, Chef! None of your
recipes today need corn...
Forget about that!
Thanks to Doux, I thought
up an even better dish!
I guess Lady Doux helped Thaiti out.
She's grown into such a kind child.
Okay, everyone! You don't
need to rush so much!
Wh-Wh-What is this?!
What is this? It's super good!
I've never eaten something so delicious!
B-But why do we slaves get some, too?
There's enough for everyone! Here, Doux.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Look, Doux is serving them food.
U-Unbelievable!
I want to eat food that
Doux serves me, too.
Er, stop being jealous and
stop her, Your Majesty!
What are you doing?
I came in time for the Face
Reveal Ceremony and...
Are you the dunce serving
these lesser humans food?
What was I supposed to do?
Pawpaw!
Doux said she wanted to eat with everyone.
Silence!
It's your failure that you let
her words sway your judgment.
Stop her at once.
Or else...
I will turn everyone involved
into slabs of meat right now.
S-So this is the aura of
the previous demon king Zareth,
said to make even demons tremble...
Brilliant! I'm sure that Lord Zareth
will be able to stop Lady Doux!
Pawpaw!
This is for you, Pawpaw!
Doux made yours special and made
your veggies into stars, Pawpaw.
Make sure you eat all the stars!
Doux!
You made this just for me?
It's hopeless. I need to
hurry and do something.
Oh my. It's always so lively around Doux.
L-Lady Dahaka. This is no laughing matter.
This is all happening because Lady
Doux is spreading her kindness.
Oh. But what do you think?
After seeing this, I'm fairly certain
she'll be just fine tomorrow.
Huh?
I see! So this is why you
wanted us to go find Doux.
Your Majesty?
Doux, it was really yummy.
Thanks for the food!
Big Bro, this is super tasty.
Isn't it great that we
came to this castle, Bro?
There's plenty more!
Lady Doux!
I've made a new magic potion!
See?
Huh?
Wow, amazing!
I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!
Isn't it amazing?
I just learned this recently,
but basically everyone who lives in
the demon castle are Doux's friends.
H-Her friends?
Demons and humans.
Magical beasts and witches.
Possibly even others...
Everyone who's encountered Doux at
least once mysteriously gather to her.
That's why there's no need to worry.
Doux isn't scared of anything
so there's no need to force her to act
a certain way or say certain things.
As long as she's herself,
she will look dignified to everyone.
Yes, you're right.
I-Is this really okay?